[Music]
[Música]
Then what do you send me Lili? I simply want to
luego qué me mandas Lili yo simplemente
say that I feel very proud to
decir que me siento muy orgullosa de
belong to this great family and to
pertenecer a esta gran familia y de
share the nights with you, I will
compartir las noches con vosotros no me
never tire of saying it. Oh well,
cansaré nunca de decirlo Ah bueno lo del
not about the hats, which apparently is
gorras no que por lo visto está
making me green, no. That's what you
poniéndome verde no Eso es lo que me has
made me see. Before that, I wanted to
hecho a ver yo antes de eso quería
comment on one thing, which is that today, of
comentar una cosa que es que hoy
course, there are things that really Look, I don't
claro yo hay cosas que de verdad Mira No
know what example to give you right now,
sabría qué ejemplo poneros ahora mismo
but there was something, what it was, family, there
pero hubo un qué es lo que fue familia
was something that happened to him, I don't remember what it
hubo algo que le pasó a él no me acuerdo
was, but it was something serious. Don't you
que es lo que fue pero fue algo grave no
want to browse the
quieres Navegar de forma segura en
internet safely and also access all the
internet y además acceder a todo el
content of your favorite platforms
contenido de tus plataformas favoritas
like Netflix, HBO Max, or Disney Plus. Cyber
como Netflix hbo Max o Disney Plus Cyber
Ghost VPN And I don't know if you know,
Ghost VPN Y es que no sé si lo sabes
but there is content that is not available in your country
pero hay contenidos que en tu país no
and with this little trick
están disponibles y con este truquillo
you can access all the content wherever you
puedes acceder a todo el contenido estés
are. I don't know if you know what a
donde estés no sé si sabes lo que es una
VPN is, but it's an extension that you put on
VPN pero es una extensión que le pones a
your internet with which you mask your IP
tu internet con la que en mascaras la IP
and apart from browsing completely safely
y aparte de Navegar completamente seguro
and anonymously without anyone being able to know
y anónimo sin que nadie pueda saber
who you are and where you are.  it is used to
quién eres y dónde estás Te sirve para
access some content that is
acceder a algunos contenidos que están
blocked in your country there are movies and
bloqueados en tu país hay películas y
series on your favorite platforms that
series en tus plataformas favoritas que
are not available there are
no están disponible hay programas de
television programs for example on mediaset
televisión por ejemplo en mediaset
content that if you try to watch them outside
contenidos que si los intentas ver fuera
of Spain they have a geoblock that does not
de España tienen un geobloqueo que no te
allow you Well with cyberghost VPN that is
lo permite Pues con cyberghost VPN eso
over Apart from being protected and
se acabó Aparte de estar protegido y
browsing anonymously you will be able to
navegando bajo la anonimato podrás
access content from all over the
acceder a los contenidos de todo el
planet you will also have Total privacy
planeta además tendrás privacidad Total
since it keeps your connection private and
ya que mantiene tu conexión en privado y
protects your data ultra fast speed to
protege tus datos velocidad ultrarápida
eliminate the lake in any
para eliminar el lago en cualquier juego
online game with which you can enjoy live
online con los que podrás disfrutar de
streams without interruptions and as I have already
directos sin interrupciones y como ya os
told you Freedom to access all the
he dicho Libertad para acceder a todo el
content on the planet wherever and whenever
contenido del planeta dónde y cuando
you want also take advantage of HD an 83%
quieras además aprovecha HD un 83 por de
discount using the link that I
descuento utilizando el enlace que te
leave you in the description of this video and be
dejo en la descripción de este vídeo y
careful because you can try Cyber ​​Ghost VPN
ojo porque puedes probar Cyber Ghost VPN
45 days without obligation and if you are not
45 días sin compromiso y si no te
convinced you ask for a refund and they
convence pides el reembolso y te
will give you your belly back So don't wait any
devuelven la panza Así que no esperes
longer to protect your connection and improve
más para proteger tu conexión y aumentar
your internet experience run the
tu experiencia en internet corré el
click on the link in the description and take
click al enlace de la descripción y
advantage of this super offer Cyber ​​Ghost
aprovecha esta superoferta Cyber Ghost
VPN to browse completely free and
VPN para navegar completamente libre y
secure continue with the video I don't
seguro seguimos con el vídeo No me
remember what  something serious happened to him that
acuerdo qué cosa le pasó algo grave que
I
yo la
condemned him two or three times in which there have
condenéis dos o tres ocasiones en las
been people who have crossed
que ha habido gente que se ha pasado de
the line with him and I have condemned them I
la raya con él y yo las he condenado O
mean no I'm not at all obsessed
sea yo no no estoy para nada obsesionado
with him for me he is an
con él para mí es una persona
indifferent person he makes me very
indiferente a mí me causa mucha
indifferent he is a little character that
indiferencia es un personajillo que
sometimes I even find funny
algunas veces incluso me hace gracia de
here on the internet you know but from there
aquí de del internet sabes pero de ahí a
I wish him evil or I am aware
que yo le deseo un mal o esté pendiente
of him or he puts on some clothes and I
de él o él se ponga una ropa y yo me
put on the clothes or he fights and I fight
ponga la ropa o él se pele y me pele
just like him you know what I'm telling you I mean
igual que él sabes lo que te digo O sea
no I don't have that I know that he is a fan I know that he has
no no tengo esa yo sé que él es fan yo
been a fan in fact he
sé que él ha sido un fan de hecho él
himself has said it publicly on a
mismo lo ha dicho públicamente en un
lot of occasions but well to me
montón de ocasiones pero bueno a mí ya
since he dedicates himself to applauding people who
que él se dedique a aplaudir a gente que
commit certain crimes quite serious
comete ciertos delitos bastante fuertes
against me that already escapes me a
contra mí a mí eso ya se me escapa un
little bit with how good a person he is okay he
poco con lo buena persona que él es vale
says he is that he says he is a
que él dice ser que él dice que es una
beautiful person and and so good no that
persona bellísima y y tan buena no que
he is well look It turns out that yesterday
es él pues mira Resulta ser que ayer
Well we already realized A few days ago
Bueno ya nos dimos cuenta Hace unos días
that he followed r r  beiruti okay This is a
que siguió a r r beiruti vale Este es un
Venezuelan who lives in Miami now he is
venezolano que vive en Miami ahora está
in the United States recently he was in
en Estados Unidos hace poco estuvo en la
jail for some death threats he
cárcel por por unas amenazas de muerte
made to a person Okay and this one
que hizo a una persona Vale y este pues
was a friend of Dallas for a while
fue un amigo de Dallas durante un tiempo
and it ended badly no and Juanjo now
y acabó acabaron mal no y y Juanjo ahora
well has started following him okay many of us
pues lo ha empezado a seguir vale muchos
remember him in the salsería chat
le recordamos en el chat de la salsería
giving you Palmas before collaborating together
dándote Palmas antes de colaborar juntos
yes yes Lili I mean he donated he became a
sí sí Lili o sea él donaba se hacía
member eh He asked me for an interview whether I
miembro eh Me pedía entrevista sea que
was a fan it's undeniable no but well here you
era fan es innegable no pero bueno aquí
have him following raed okay
lo tenéis siguiendo a raed vale
eh it turns out that yesterday he realized
eh resulta que ayer se daría cuenta de
the huge barbarity that he committed no
la de la gran barbaridad que hizo no
because apart from insulting me for my
porque que aparte de insultarme por el
physique That a Juanjo insults me
físico Que a mí que un Juanjo me insulte
for my physique You see you don't e To me that
por el físico Ya ves tú no e A mí que me
a Juanjo insults me for my physique I mean it
insulte un Juanjo por el físico o sea es
's the most ridiculous thing that can be
que es lo más ridículo que te pueden
said to you during the day the first is
decir durante el día lo primero es
because I don't consider myself ugly
porque no Considero que yo e sea feo
let's say it like that no I consider myself to
vamos a decirlo así no Considero que yo
be ugly and secondly because yes I consider
sea feo y lo segundo porque sí Considero
that you are a lot I mean things
que lo eres tú un montón o sea las cosas
as they are okay  But well I don't see
como son vale Pero bueno no veo a ojos
sad eyes talking about this Thanks for your
tristes hablando de esto Gracias por tu
publicity or rather this tet Juanjo deleted it
publicidad o sea este tet lo borró
yesterday okay he published it I don't know how
Juanjo ayer vale lo publicó no sé cuánto
long ago and he deleted it they sent it to me and it
tiempo y lo borró me me lo mandaron e y
's a tweet in which raed well he is
es un tweet en el que raed pues está
accusing this it has a very long Lore
acusando esto tiene un Lore muy largo
that is not the topic of the day okay Yes it will be
que no es el tema del día vale Sí será
the topic of the day then the salsería Okay
el tema del día luego la salsería Vale
but r was a guy who made
pero r era un tío que hacía
cryptocurrencies with Dallas and now they
criptomonedas con el Dallas y ahora se
fought And then uh they are accusing
pelearon Y entonces eh se están acusando
each other of fraud no I mean where
mutuamente de estafa no O sea donde
before r supported Dallas and defended him
antes r apoyaba a Dallas y lo defendía
from all the accusations now
de todas las acusaciones ahora de
suddenly he talks to delox with with the complete
repente se habla con delox con con todo
opposite okay with all the
lo contrario vale con toda la gente
contrary people now delos is not a
contraria ya delos no es ningún
scammer already Christ bru well anyway it is
estafador ya Cristo bru bueno en fin es
a very extensive Lore that is from the
un Lore muy extenso que es de la
salsería no the move is that Juanjo A
salsería no la movida es que Juanjo Hace
few days ago Precisely in one of these live
unos días Precisamente en uno de estos
broadcasts that I dedicate eh he said that he did
directos que me dedico eh él dijo que él
not talk about cryptocurrencies do you remember
no hablaba de criptomonedas os acordáis
that he said no no I do not comment anything about him
que dijo no no yo no comento nada de él
I do not comment anything about cryptocurrencies I do
yo no comento nada de criptomonedas yo
not comment anything about others and I told you if
no comento nada de otro y os dije si
comment if you commented Juanjo about
comenta si comentaste Juanjo de
cryptocurrencies you commented at the
criptomonedas lo comentaste en su
time and look boom again It's that you
momento y mira pum otra vez Es que
always lie dude you're a mythomaniac you're a
siempre mientes tío eres mitómano eres
hypocrite and on top of that you're bad you're bad very
hipócrita y encima Eres malo eres malo
bad dude very bad person okay You don't
malísimo tío malísima persona vale No
have a [ __ ] clue about this Juanjo I mean
tienes ni [__] idea de esto Juanjo O sea
you're reading this text about
tú estás leyendo este texto sobre
cryptocurrency and you don't know who's
criptomoneda y no sabes quién tiene
right if Dallas or RAED because you don't
razón si Dallas o raed porque tú no
understand cryptocurrency You're just
entiendes de criptomoneda Apenas estás
starting to know that there are hotels that
empezando a conocer que hay hoteles que
have pools on the roof you're going to know
tienen piscinas en el techo vas a saber
about cryptocurrency creature This is okay
de criptomoneda criatura Esto vale
summary of everything family this is this
resumen de todo familia esto es este
accusing the other of one thing eh that no that no that it's
acusándole al otro de una cosa eh que no
nothing that it's not going to get
que no que no es nada que no va a llegar
anywhere and these are cryptocurrency things that
en nada y son cosas de criptomoneda que
work like that they work like that okay
funcionan así que funcionan asá vale
but the thing is Juan no he doesn't understand
pero es que Juan no no entiende de
cryptocurrencies he doesn't know if RAE is
criptomonedas no sabe si RAE tiene la
right or not but he just
razón o no la tiene pero él simplemente
takes it And says Well I don't see sad eyes
coge Y dice Bueno no veo a ojos tristes
talking about this like no How come no Of
hablando de esto como que no Cómo que no
course at night when
Claro que sí por la noche cuando llegó
the salsería live came on I talked about the subject and
el directo de salsería hablé del tema y
you had to delete the tweet why You get
tú tuviste que borrar el tweet para qué
ahead of yourself I'll talk when the
Te adelantas hablaré cuando sea el
live is  from the salsería No but dude if
directo de la salsería No pero guajo si
you're interested in scams and
te interesan las las estafas y los
deceptions and cryptocurrencies you have
engaños y las criptomonedas tienes a
delox incredible track record you have Peppa
delox increíble historial tienes a Peppa
and the 240 you've had it you've had it on
y los 240 lo has tenido la has tenido en
your channel you have Loli Huerta who
tu canal tienes a Loli Huerta que le
promised your friend Tania that everything that
prometió a tu amiga Tania que todo lo
her channel generated she was going to
que generase su canal lo iba a
multiply by two and she was going to give it to
multiplicar por dos y se lo iba a dar a
an animal association there you have a
una asociación de animales ahí tienes un
lot of topics that are also about
montón de temas que también van de
deceptions and they are a little simpler
engaños y son un poco más sencillitos
than cryptocurrencies and maybe a
que las criptomonedas y a lo mejor una
person like you could understand it
persona como tú la podría entender
then if you are interested And you are so
entonces si te interesa Y estás tan
aware of those causes talk about
concienciado con esas causas habla de
Loli talk about Peppa and talk about a lot of
Loli habla de Peppa y habla de un montón
people that you are talking to
de gente con la que te estás hablando
now okay pathetic eh sad eyes Well, about the
ahora vale patetico eh ojos triste Bueno
physical issue, let's go let's go let's go let's
del tema del físico ya vamos vamos vamos
ignore it no but
a vamos a vamos a obviarlo no pero
on top of that he says Thank you for your advertising
encima dice Gracias por tu publicidad
okay and I have put this thread no Juanjo
vale y le he puesto este hilo no Juanjo
blo has deleted this publication where he
blo ha eliminado esta publicación donde
supports raed beiruti and insults me ra
apoya a raed beiruti y me insulta ra
beiruti okay so that you know who he
beiruti vale para que sepáis a quién
is supporting Juanjo r beiruti is a
está apoyando Juanjo r beiruti es un
Venezuelan  who recently acknowledged in
venezolano que reconoció últimamente en
some spaces on Twitter having done
algunos space de Twitter haber hecho
several rook pools you know what a rook
varios rook pool sabes lo que es un rook
pool is Juanjo what he is accusing
pool Juanjo de lo que está acusando aquí
Dallas of here okay that he has acknowledged having done it in some spaces
a Dallas vale eso él en algunos espacios
okay And I
ha reconocido haberlo hecho vale Y yo
have here a series of coins
tengo aquí una serie de de monedas
too that he took out and he also did it
también que él sacó y también la hizo
Okay and at this moment RAE
Vale y en estos momentos RAE se
is on bail after being in
encuentra bajo fianza tras estar un fin
jail for a weekend for
de semana encarcelado por amenazas
serious threats contest that [ __ ] already Damn it do
graves contest esa [__] ya Maldito Sea
n't you understand that what causes me the most is that
no entiendes que lo que más me causan
the damn thing that doesn't answer my
que la [__] que no me contesta el
phone don't you
teléfono no
understand look these are some of the
entiendes mira estas son algunas de las
threats okay for which your new idol
amenazas vale por las que tu nuevo ídolo
spent a weekend locked up look today you
pasó un fin de semana encerrado mira hoy
won't be able to sleep there Neither you nor your mother
no llegas a dormir ahí Ni tú ni tu mamá
look eye you who are so aware
mira ojo tú que estás tan concienciado
of families the mothers and so on don't
con las familias las mamás y y demás no
look at what your new idol said to an
mira lo que le dijo tu nuevo ídolo a una
elderly person Neither you nor your mother I'm going to
persona mayor Ni tú ni tu mamá la voy a
peel her you know what that means in
pelar sabes lo que significa en
Venezuela I'm going to peel her Juanjo Look for it
Venezuela la voy a pelar Juanjo Búscalo
this is the police report Eh This is not
esto es el parte policial Eh Esto no es
a video of Javi Oliveira or Dallas
un vídeo de Javi oliveira ni de Dallas
or anything This is what you support Juanjo I
ni nada Esto es lo que tú apoyas Juanjo
already know where your mother is I'm going to  peel it I'm
Ya sé dónde está tu mamá la voy a pelar
going to peel it and I'm going to peel it You're not going to
la voy a pelar y la voy a pel No vais a
get home You're not going to get to sleep
llegar a casa No vais a llegar a dormir
there and what you're hearing in the
ahí y este que estáis escuchando de
background is raay yelling At an
fondo es raay gritándole A una
ex answer that [ __ ] Damn it don't
ex contestes esa [__] Maldito Sea no
understand that what causes me the most is that
entiendes que lo que más me causan que
damn it that doesn't answer my
la [__] que no me contesta el
phone Do you understand me I answered and he
teléfono Me entiendes Me contest ya
has also Thanked me for the
también me ha Agradecido por la
publicity have you seen it here he doesn't
publicidad lo habéis visto aquí no me
tell me Thank you for the publicity since
dice Gracias por la publicidad al haber
I have mentioned it again lately his
vuelto yo a mencionarlo últimamente sus
viewers have improved a bit Although it is still the
espectadores han mejorado un poco Aunque
least seen in the
sigue siendo el menos visto en la
theme of the heart okay here we have
temática del corazón vale aquí tenemos
yesterday's statistics Juanjo Of course you have
las estadísticas de ayer Juanjo Claro tú
Juanjo today on your Twitter and you
has cogido Juanjo hoy en tu Twitter y
have published this this capture okay
has publicado esta esta captura vale Por
Why Because you with your great interview and
qué Porque tú con tu gran entrevista y
your new shirt interviewing Amador
tu camisa nueva entrevistando a Amador
you had a peak of 2600 viewers And
tuviste un pico de 2600 espectadores Y
telesalseo yesterday without anything special had
telesalseo ayer sin nada especial tuvo
2300 Wow Juanjo Congratulations Congratulations
2300 Wow Juanjo Enhorabuena Enhorabuena
for having gotten 300 viewers with
por haberme sacado 300 espectadores con
an interview that was your interview of the
una entrevista que era tu entrevista del
year on your main channel to my
año en tu canal principal a mi canal
tertiary channel Wow Congratulations if you feel
terciario Wow Enhorabuena si te sientes
good and  winner with that Juanjo 300
bien y triunfador con eso Juanjo 300
viewers to a channel of 180,000
espectadores a un canal de 180.000
subscribers tertiary because you have not
suscriptores terciario porque no has
published everything in full Look Antonio
publicado todo completo Mira Antonio
David Flores his peak was 3300 mik
David flores su pico fue de 3300 mik
Vasco had 6000 viewers yesterday Javi
Vasco tuvo ayer 6000 espectadores Javi
Oliveira 3000 viewers me with my
oliveira 3000 espectadores yo con mi
main channel me with my main channel
canal princip yo con mi canal principal
yesterday Juanjo went back to bathe but are you
ayer Juanjo volv a bañar pero tú estás
happy because you got
contento porque le has sacado tú a mi
300 viewers from my Third channel Wow and you
Tercer canal 300 espectadores Wow y por
gave him 500 from Troy because if he
le has dado 500 de Troya que si no me
hadn't gotten 600 from me my mother But oh well He
hubiera sacado 600 madre mía Pero bueno
thanks me No it's not the first
Me da las gracias No no es la primera
time he's rubbed shoulders with someone convicted
vez que se codea con alguien condenado
his star collaborator Amador Moedano
su colaborador estrella Amador moedano
was convicted years ago by court
fue condenado hace años por el juzgado
number 2 of San Lucas de Barrameda
número 2 de San Lucas de barrameda
because his dogs attacked a
porque sus perros atacaron a una niña de
14 year old girl causing her after-effects Amador never
14 años causándole secuelas Amador nunca
apologized to the family Lucar de
se disculpó con la familia lucar de
Barrameda has sentenced Amador Muedano
barrameda ha condenado a Amador muedano
to pay about 2000 to the 13 year old girl
a pagar unos 2000 a la niña de 13 años a
whom  they bit her dogs in the fall
la que mordieron sus perros en el otoño
of 2014 and caused wounds on her
de 2014 y le causaron heridas en sus
breasts what I want is that money to
pechos yo lo que quiero ese dinero para
give to my girl to take the girl the
darle mi niña para cogerle la niña la
creature the rays the faith to
criatura los rayos la fe para que le
remove those marks that her breasts have That's
quite esas marcas que tiene el pecho Eso
the only thing I want the breasts
es lo único que yo quiero los pechitos
what is that I don't know I don't know I read so ugly
lo que está que no se no se Leo tan feo
no the judge in his ruling qu Juanjo they
no el juez en su fallo qu Juanjo me
are telling me here that today
están diciendo por aquí que hoy estabas
you were on your secondary channel live with
tú en tu canal secundario en directo con
600 people 600 people on your
600 personas 600 personas en tu canal
secondary channel Juano it is duly
secundario Juano está debidamente
proven that that afternoon while
probado que Aquella tarde mientras
Amador was having a drink at a kiosk
Amador estaba tomando algo en un quiosco
his dogs were running loose in a square in
sus perros andaban sueltos en una plaza
Chipiona at the moment in which they attacked
de chipiona momento en el que atacaron a
the little girl who was
la pequeña que se encontraba allí
playing there my daughter was outside with a
jugando mi hija estaba í afuera con un
sandwich and a juice and right off the bat she
bocadillo y un zumito y de buena primera
approached the dog and jumped on the girl I
se acercó al perro y se lanzó a la niña
scratched him the dog was
le di un arañazo perro allí estaba
sitting there in a beer that's what he
sentado en una cerveza es lo que ha
declared there in the Ju nothing to do with
declarado allí en el Ju nada que ver con
the version that Amador gave us a month ago
la versión que nos daba Amador hace mes
defending the innocence of my dog ​​because it is
defender la inocencia de mi perro porque
a dog that is is  a
se trata de un perro que es es un
little lamb good little lamb a little lamb that
corderito buen corderito un corderito
bit a minor a little lamb
que que mordió a una menor un corderito
Hey guajo you know that Amador lied and said
Oye guajo sabes que Amador mintió y dijo
that it wasn't his dog that had bitten
que no era su perro el que había mordido
the girl and then he had to make a
a la niña y luego tuvo que hacer una
sentence recognizing the facts well
sentencia reconociendo los hechos bueno
you family those of you who are here that I do
ustedes familia los que estáis aquí que
n't know if today I haven't set a target eh
no sé si hoy no os he puesto objetivo eh
today we have set a target But well
hoy nosos he puesto objetivo Pero bueno
in you remember what a mess Juanjo
em ustedes recuerdan la Que Lio Juanjo
Because someone compared a photo of him with
Porque alguien comparó una foto suya con
his wife with a photo of me with my wife
su mujer con una foto mía con mi mujer
saying what you ask for and what you get do
diciendo lo que pides y lo que te llega
you remember what the gachon caused with
os acordáis de la que lió el gachon con
that nonsense surely you do remember
esa tontería seguramente sí lo recordáis
No the mess the gachon caused Because someone
No la que lió el gachon Porque alguien
compared a photo of him with his wife
comparó una foto de él con su mujer con
with a photo of me with my wife don't you remember
con una foto mía con mi mujer no os
No well Look who
acordáis No pues Mirad a Quién apoya
Juan joblon supports Look what he does Who
Juan joblon Mirad lo que hace a Quién
Juan joblon supports Because I'm still
apoya Juan joblon Porque todavía estoy
starting mind you I'm only
empezando ojo que es que solamente estoy
starting I told him today and I laughed my ass off I
empezando se lo dije hoy y me cagado en
told him I told him he comes to
la risa se los dije le dije llega a
publish on his Instagram a baby And he says that the
publicar en su Instagram un bebé Y dice
baby is his and I'm leaving I'm going to
que el bebé es de él y me voy voy a
come and I'm going to make fun of the [ __ ] baby and it
venir y me voy a burlar del [__] bebé y
tastes like [ __ ] to me and it tastes like a lot of
me sabe a [__] y me sabe a muchísima
[ __ ] to them it tastes like [ __ ] all of them
[__] a ellos le sabe [__] todo ellos
a kiss Adrian the extra is calling you a
un beso Adrián el extra te está llamando
slanderer Tell the extra that I know to stop
difamador Dile al extra que se que deje
doing his daily task of whitewashing
de de hacer su tarea diaria de blanquear
criminals which is the only thing that
delincuentes que es a lo único que se
the whitewasher does Do you think it's
dedica la blanqueadora crees que es
funny He thinks it's funny Oh
chistosito él cree que es chistosito Ay
how funny, right? Oh how funny, to go laugh there
qué risa no Ay qué risa ir a reírme allá
with a rand map of mentally [ __ ] people
con un mapa rand de retrasados mentales
who are the ones who see him who don't
que son los que lo ven a él que no
have the brains for this They don't have the
tienen cerebro para esto no tienen
brains for this It's impossible for them eh
cerebro para esto no les da imposible eh
the mentally [ __ ] people who follow
los retrasados mentales que lo siguen a
him think he says ha Well You
él creen que dice ja Pues Tú solito te
answered yourself prisoner Well I am a
has contestado recluso Bueno yo soy
prisoner well his wife is a [ __ ] catfish
recluso pues su mujer es un [__] bagre
Ah I am a prisoner Ah I am a prisoner
Ah yo soy un recluso Ah yo soy recluso
I am imprisoned at this moment well
yo estoy recluido en este momento bueno
his wife is a [ __ ] vagre next to
su mujer es un maldito vagre al lado de
mine his wife is a [ __ ] catfish and
la mía su mujer es un maldito bagre y
What's going on What's he going to say I cried to me she
Qué pasa Qué va a decir llore a mí me
seems like a catfish I  I wouldn't touch her with a
parece un bagre yo no la toco ni con un
pointer l not with a pointer l this chick
puntero l ni con un puntero l esta tipa
on the [ __ ] road would have a chance to even
en la [__] via tendría chance ni
get close to me by my standards because
acercarse a mí por mis estándares pues
unfortunately for me this girlfriend his
Lamentablemente para mí esta novia su
wife his wife her thing a [ __ ]
mujer suya esposa cosa suya un maldito
catfish And what is she going to say that she's going to
bagre Y qué va a decir qu me va a
report me for saying that she's a catfish she's
denunciar por decir que es un bagre es
a catfish she's horrible she's horrible what is she going to
un bagre espantosa es espantoso qué va a
say I report report report for
decir denuncio denuncio n denunciar por
saying that she's a scumbag if I say to
decir que está un vagre si a m yo digo
me what the lining of my ass comes out
lo que a mí me salga el [__] del culo
of this [ __ ] wretch Come on,
de este maldito desgraciado Vaya pues
this is a little more than your wife being
esto es un poquito más de que a tu mujer
called a croquette, dude, the one you
la llamen croqueta guajo al que tú
support that you're supporting because she
apoyas que lo estás apoyando porque me
harasses me is a little stronger no than them
acosa es un poquito más fuerte no de que
calling her a croquette no and have you seen what she
la llamen croqueta no y has visto lo que
said about my son that if I publish
ha dicho sobre mi hijo que si publico
a photo of my son they're going after the [ __ ]
una foto de mi hijo van a por el [__]
baby and you're supporting him because of this
bebé y tú lo estás apoyando por esto
Juanjo because of this you're following him do you
Juanjo por esto lo estás tú siguiendo os
also remember when Que Lio
acordáis también cuando la Que Lio
Juanjo because they went to his neighborhood and
Juanjo porque fueron a su barrio y
recorded him they played a joke on him
grabaron le gastaron una broma con la
that I wasn't with  okay Also I at the
que yo no estuve de acuerdo Además yo en
time condemn him the one who messed around with
su momento lo condenéis la que lió con
that they had gone to record in his neighborhood, on his
que habían ido a grabar a su barrio a su
street. Oh they are threatening me, do you remember
calle Ay me están amenazando os acordáis
that, okay, look what this
de eso vale pues Mirad lo que hace este
man does, his new friend, okay, he has been threatening me for weeks
señor su nuevo amigo vale lleva semanas
with coming to Seville to
amenazándome con venir a Sevilla a
attack me, that's why we are
agredirme que por esto lo estamos
reporting him, eh. Yesterday several of you contacted me and we
denunciando eh Ya ayer me contactaste
already have the way to
varios y y ya tenemos la forma de
report him in the United States, it's not
denunciarlo en Estados Unidos no vale
as expensive as I thought it can be done and
tan caro como me creía se puede hacer y
man, we are going to report him for a
hombre lo vamos a denunciar por unos
few things. RAE
cuantas de por unas cuantas de cosas RAE
has a restraining order for the
tiene una orden de alejamiento por las
threats. Yes, yes, he has a
amenazas Sí sí sí tiene orden de
restraining order. Well, this little gem, this little gem
alejamiento Pues esta joyita esta joyita
who threatens my son and who threatens my
que amenaza a mi hijo y que amenaza a mi
wife. Well, he is Juanjo's new friend,
mujer Pues es el nuevo amigo de Juanjo
whom Juanjo supports and defends, now he has
al que Juanjo apoya y defiende ahora
followed. Simply because he harasses me, I
haya seguido Simplemente porque me acosa
coincided two days in Chipion in a hotel
coincidí dos días en chipion en un hotel
with the man from the Blog yellow shirt
con el señor del Blog camisa amarilla
with palm trees and a screw-on metal cap. A show. A
con palmeras y gorra rosca chapa Un show
show yellow shirt with palm trees
Un show camisa amarilla con con palmeras
and a screw-on metal cap. A kiss. Gustavo Well
y gorra rosca chapa un beso Gustavo Pues
there you have it, following a person
ahí lo tenéis siguiendo a una persona
because he is harassing me, that's
porque me está haciendo ese acoso ese
you  Juanjo you're showing off son you've
eres Juanjo te estás luciendo hijo
been showing off for a while
llevas una temporadita que te estás
come on I already knew who it was eh I already
luciendo vamos yo ya sabía quién era eh
saw you he tells you game over there can there can
Ya te calé te dice el game over ahí
people Search Game
puede ahí puede la gente Buscar Game
Over Juan joblo okay people can find it
Over Juan joblo vale que lo encuentre la
em kata Don't tell me Javi I gave you
gente em kata No me digas Javi te puse
information about a lawyer in mdx well
información de una abogada en mdx pues
kata I'll look at it later ok you
kata lo miro luego vale me habéis
sent me a lot of things I'll see all
mandado un montón de cosas veré todas
the options but come on it's going to be
las opciones pero vamos que se va a
done it can be done This week
hacer se puede hacer Ya esta semana
something will probably come up this week
seguramente salga algo esta semana sale
something will come up eh Yes yes Virginia exactly
sale algo eh Sí sí Virginia exactamente
from what they've been telling me today I
por lo que me han estado diciendo hoy
was talking on the phone with someone
estuve hablando por teléfono con alguien
and from what they've
y por lo que me está por lo que me han
been telling me in the United States his
estado diciendo en en Estados Unidos se
hair is falling out but let's say but it's not really
le cae el pelo pero vamos pero bien
fallen out but let's say there's no
caído no pero vamos que no hay ninguna
doubt I mean you've seen a little eh you
duda o sea habéis visto un poco eh
've seen a little but there's a lot more
habéis visto un poco pero hay mucho más
going on than that I'll deal with it later at the
pasa que eso ya luego lo trato en la
salseria eh well we've already been
salsería Eh bueno ya lo hemos estado
dealing with it at the salseria But there's a
tratando en la salsería Pero hay mucho
lot more there's been
más hay mucho más lleva semanas
threatening me insulting me for weeks yesterday
amenazándome insultándome ayer abrió un
the guy started a live stream and called me eh  the picture of me
directo el tipo y me puso eh la foto mía
when I started the physical change,
de cuando yo empecé el cambio físico
well he stood there to try to
pues se puso ahí para intentar
humiliate me saying look, she has
humillarme a decir mira tiene las
tits like a minor's, I don't know what. I mean,
tetitas como las menores no sé qué O sea
some things, I mean, they're going to, they're going to
unas cosas o sea lo van a lo van a lo
lock him up again for sure, eh, yes, they locked him up,
van a volver a encerrar seguro eh si lo
yes, he has told me more than what he
encer si me ha dicho a mí ya más de lo
said to the guy with what with him, the one who
que le dijo al tío con lo con el el que
locked him up, they are going to lock him up 100%
lo encerraron lo van a encerrar 100%
100% and we are seeing how to do it but
100% y estamos viendo cómo hacerlo pero
come on, there is no doubt that what
vamos es que no hay ninguna duda que lo
that man is doing is not legal but
que hace ese hombre no Es legal pero es
who would think otherwise who would
que quién pensaba lo contrario quién
think otherwise Estela stela eh No no
pensaba lo contrario Estela stela eh No
no Virginia Several people have already sent me
no no Virginia Ya me han mandado varias
ways to do it
varias personas los modos de hacerlo
first you have to file a complaint that
primero hay que poner una denuncia que
it won't cost me money I think Well, I'm not
eso no me cuesta dinero creo Bueno no os
going to comment on it okay but let's go from what I
lo voy a comentar vale pero vamos por lo
've seen more or less the total eh It
que he visto más o menos el total eh No
's not something that I cannot assume the
es una cosa que no pueda yo asumir de
expenses says gromer It is a crime to criticize a
gastos dice gromer Es delito criticar un
man's physique Of course not but
físico hombre Por supuesto que no pero
putting a person there to harass them no
poner a una persona para acosarla ahí no
eh he is a stalker but There are many more
eh es un acosador pero Hay muchas más
things, it's not just criticizing a  physical
cosas no solamente es criticar un físico
is humiliating every day humiliate humiliate
es humillar todos los días humillar
look at a [ __ ] catfish of your wife
humillar mira un [__] bagre de tu mujer
a [ __ ] brager and if you put the picture of the
un [__] brager y si pones la foto del
child I'm going after the child man of course it
niño voy a por el niño hombre pues claro
's a crime my children grumer I know that
que es delito hijos mío grumer yo sé que
maybe it's yours But no of
a lo mejor es lo tuyo Pero no por
course it's a crime but it's not only that
supuesto que es delito pero no solamente
eh he started writing to people that
es eso eh se puso a escribirle a gente a
we're interviewing
la que a la que vamos entrevistando
when when we interview for example
cuando cuando entrevistamos por ejemplo
Javier urra he started writing to
a Javier urra se puso a escribirle a
Javier urra the
Javier urra también se pone a escribir
people that we're going to
la gente a la que a la que vamos a
interview that we've interviewed also start writing
entrevistar a la que hemos entrevistado
trying to scare them away a stalker is a
intentando espantarlos un acosador es un
stalker I mean I'm completely
acosador o sea estoy completamente
sure that it's going to have
seguro de que de que va a tener
repercussions in the United States without a doubt
repercusión en Estados Unidos sin duda
we're going without a doubt well let's see what
vamos sin duda bueno a ver qué es lo que
Lili yosa sends me from belonging to this
me manda Lili yosa de pertenecer a esta
great family and from sharing the nights
gran familia y de compartir las noches
with you I will never tire of
con vosotros no me cansaré nunca de
saying it that we continue to be at the top of
decirlo que seguimos siendo el top de
wonderful people eh what did I say I noara
gente maravillosa eh que di yo yo noara
in places where you see the chat that is
en sitios donde ves el chat que está
looking for trouble insulting and it's that on
buscando follón insultando y es que
top of that it is allowed it's what no no  I just
encima se permite es lo que no no acabo
understood no and and apart from that they don't respect
de entender no y y aparte no respetan a
anonymous people they don't respect the opinions
gente anónima no respetan las opiniones
of others it's the imposition of Oh today
de los demás es la imposición de Ay hoy
that has been striped that has less
que ha estado rayado con que tiene menos
visits that has less visits than the
visitas que tiene menos visitas que la
pppa no longer has less viewers than
pppa ya no tiene menos espectadores que
Pepa no longer gives his criteria eh it is to
la [__] ya no de sus criterios eh es
continuously discredit and defame not
desacreditar y difamar continuamente no
only one but 40 channels Juanjo and that
solo a uno sino 40 canales Juanjo y que
in general it is a voracious hatred of everything
en general es un odio voraz a todo lo
that can overshadow you or everything that
que te pueda hacer sombra o todo lo que
can give you money but it is true that
te pueda dar dinero pero es verdad que
I notice that there are changes eh There are people who
que noto que hay cambios eh Hay gente
are and who are preparing
que está y que está preparando
things there are people who are grouping together and
cosas hay gente que se está agrupando y
who are preparing things yes harassment
que está preparando cosas sí acosos
Juanjo harassment of the people that you are
Juanjo acosos a la gente a la que tú vas
following and you are supporting things By the
siguiendo y vas apoyando a cosos Por
way Juan you have a video on your channel
cierto Juan tienes un vídeo en tu canal
that you have not deleted yet do not
que no has borrado todavía ya no lo
delete it because we have downloaded it go tea
borres porque lo hemos descargado vá tea
what you thought of miare eh
lo que opinabas de miare eh colega vaya
mate what you thought of miare wow but
tela lo que opinabas de miare vaya pero
wow what you thought of miare how you
vay tela lo que opinabas de miare cómo
put it that if casa Partner that if no
la pusiste que si casa Partner que si no
go go eh But  well eh it's going to be a
vaya vaya eh Pero bien eh vá tela vay
mess eh anyone would say well we'll
tela eh cualquiera diría bueno lo vamos
see but gosh what he thought of her
a ver pero vatela lo que opinaba de ella
eh things eh there comes a point where it gets
eh cosas eh llega un punto en el que
tiring Juanjo it's really tiring Because
cansa Juanjo cansa muchísimo Porque
also apart from that you can see
además aparte se les va viendo el
everyone's true colors Yes because it's a and b It's
plumero a todos Sí porque es a y b
always the same with each person air air
Siempre es lo mismo con cada person aire
I was laughing Juanjo the
aire yo a mí me daba la risa Juanjo la
interview with Amador isn't interesting
entrevista de Amador no es interesante
but then you stand up and you do three
pero luego te plantas y te haces tres
live shows or two live shows talking about him
directos o dos directos hablando de él
I piss myself or whatever stupid thing they
me meeo o cualquier estup que se
make up whatever stupid thing they make up
inventen cualquier estup que se inventen
I would only ask you as a
yo que solo te preguntaría tú como
spectator because you were also there during
espectadora porque tú estuviste también
the time when I was with my
la época de de cuando estaba yo con mi
mother sick and she's there blue I
madre enferma y esta ahí azul eso yo
think that's the most innocuous at that time I don't
creo que es lo más ino en aquel época no
stop to think No but I don't know why
me par a pensar No pero no sé por qué
I'm so stupid Ho I don't know what happened Ho
estoy tan culo Ho no sé qué pasado Ho
that you as a spectator who has seen
que tú como espectadora que has visto
all this how it gets to you and then people
todo esto cómo se te queda y luego gente
also looking for firewood is that Juanjo you have
buscando también leña es que Juanjo
been receiving TR years well four
llevas TR años recibiendo bueno cuatro
receiving but Virginia says they can
recibiendo pero dice Virginia le pueden
even deport him man Virginia Well you
hasta deportar hombre Virginia Pues tú
tell me Virginia Well you  you will say if they are
me dirás Virginia Pues tú me dirás si lo
going to deport him if he also already has a
van a deportar si ya tiene además una
case that has the trial he has taken out
causa que tiene el juicio ha sacado
now Pablo now we will see him in the
ahora Pablo ahora lo veremos en la
salsería if he already has a case pending
salsería si ya tiene una causa pendiente
trial eh For what I just
de juicio eh Por eso que os acabo de
showed you imagine another cause even
enseñar imagínate á otra causa todavía
worse Of course they are going to deport him but
peor Claro que lo van a deportar pero
firewood to I think that this the platform a
leña a yo creo que esto la plataforma un
d that apag promos it can a des the
d que apag promos se puede un des la
platform is going to say that there will be a day when
plataforma va a decir que hay un día que
the fuses will go out that as long as you
se apague los plomos que nada más que le
leave the fuses to your friend Loli Huerta
dejes los plomos a tu amiga Loli Huerta
your friend Peppa your friend r and you
a tu amiga Peppa a tu amigo r y a ti
so that you can mess with the physiques of
para que te metas con con los físicos de
the women that you want
las mujeres a las que a ti te de la gana
the platform is going to pay the fuses of
la plataforma va a pagar los plomos de
whoever you don't like whoever
de quien a ti no te guste de quien te
exposes you to
exponga a
pas when it was the issue of the doll for a
pas cuando fue el tema de la muñeca po
while when parar I ar with super chat
tiempo cuando empar I ar con super chat
all that roll and and it already started there there already
todo ese rollo y y ya empezó ahí ahí ya
then there was already the massacre
entonces ahí ya era la masacre
observing who they donated more what they
observando a quién donaban más lo que
donated I remember that follower of
donaban me acuerdo de aquella seguidora
yours who had made a super chat with you It
tuya que te había hecho un super chat Me
seems to me that  he had confused that he
parece que se había confundido en que te
wanted to send you 20 and it was 200 or something like that
quería mandar 20 y fueron 200 o algo así
when we could it is prohibited
yamos cuando pudimos está prohibido
YouTube does not let you return the
YouTube no te deja devolver los los
sites that made you the lady
sitios que te hicieron la señora
appearing in all the sites to
apareciendo en todos los sitios a
corroborate is that the serious thing was not that is
corroborar es que lo gra lo grave no fue
what they invented that there was
eso es que lo que se inventaron que hab
a pasta they went to look for it you people the
una pasta fueron a buscarla tús gente la
madness eh I sometimes do tests like
locura eh yo a veces hago pruebas como
putting a twit for 5 seconds and flying to
poner un twit 5 segundos y volar para
see to what extent they monitor me and Ah okay
ver hasta qué punto me vigilan y Ah vale
your Twin was not supporting RAE which
que tu Twin no era apoyando a RAE que
was to do a test in case they monitor you
era lo para hacer una prueba por si te
Ah wow Yes yes dude you were supporting
Ah vaya Sí sí guajo que estabas apoyando
a guy and you are supporting him because you
a un tío y lo estás apoyando porque lo
still follow him only and exclusively
sigues todavía solo y exclusivamente
because he harasses me because you are not
porque me acosa porque a ti no te
interested in cryptocurrencies at all dude
interesa para nada las criptomonedas
you have not followed RAE for any
guajo tú no has seguido a RAE por ningún
other issue you follow him only and
otro tema lo sigues única y
exclusively because he has started
exclusivamente porque ha puesto a
harassing me threaten me harass my
acosarme a amenazarme a acosar a mi
wife and threaten my son that's you
mujer y amenazar a mi hijo ese eres tú
Juanjo not the lamb Ay pocito I am
Juanjo no el corderito Ay pocito que soy
here from the town and I do not mess with anyone
aquí del pueblito y no me meto con nadie
no no no  no you are that one and that's how
no no no no tú eres ese y así de
obsessed you are that you followed a
obsesionado estás que has seguido a un
guy you followed that guy with the profile
tío ha seguido a ese tío con el perfil
that just has to be seen dude I mean it's
que nada más que hay que verlo tío O sea
not like I mean well I don't know him no no you haven't
que no es decir bueno no lo conozco no
followed that guy only
no no has seguido a ese tío únicamente
because he stalks me you haven't posted a tweet
porque me acosa no has puesto un twit
to see if you're being watched admit it if you've
para ver si te vigilan reconócelo si lo
been following him for a ton of days
llevas siguiendo hace un montón de días
and yesterday I caught that t no and you're like I
y ayer que cog ese t no y te quedas en
'm as watched as that
plan de que estoy tan vigilado como ese
first day but totally I mean it's
primer día pero que totalmente o sea es
one that happens from time to time to see if they
una que ha de vez en cuando para ver si
bite and bite and oh oh it was a trap it
picen y picaro y ay ay era una trampa
was a trap to see if they bite And in
era una trampa para ver si picaban Y en
this case this woman called me
este caso esta mujer a mí me llamó
crying because they had found her Don't
llorando porque la habían encontrado No
tell me how the address her
me digas cómo la dirección sus datos
personal details and and well they wanted to hire
personales y y bueno querían contratar
her so that she would talk about me that she had
con ella para que hablase de m que se
kept money and that she would
había quedado con dinero y que me
report me what are you talking about dude
denunciara qué estás hablando tío nunca
the story will never end that it
va a acabarse la historia que empezó
all started with that nonsense about the
todo con aquella tontería de de la
interview people know perfectly well what
entrevista la gente sabe perfectamente
I said all this no no no
que fue lo que yo dije todo esto no no
juo the interview wasn't what
no juo lo de la entrevista no fue lo que
you said Juanjo  about the interview everyone has already
tú dijiste Juanjo lo de la entrevista ya
told you what it was, me
te ha dicho lo que fue todo el mundo yo
Antonio David Marina everyone who
Antonio David Marina todos los que
was involved has seen it we have
estaban implicados la han visto hemos
shown all the evidence what happened in the
enseñado todas las pruebas lo de la
interview was not what you said
entrevista no fue lo que tú dijiste
Juanjo these people who
Juanjo eso se lo van a creer esta gente
follow you who don't listen to you who are not listening to you are going to believe that
que te siguen que no te escuchan que no
what happened in the interview
te están escuchando lo de la entrevista
was that you were very dirty you were very
fue que fuiste muy cochino fuiste muy
dirty to me that it gave you a lot of
cochino conmigo que te dio un montón de
repercussions I gave you a lot of
repercusión te di un montón de
publicity and a lot of content
publicidad y un montón de contenido
we had a program some live shows in
teníamos un programa unos directos en el
which one day it was on your channel and the other day
que tocaba un día en tu canal y otro día
on mine and when when you you
en el mío y cuando cuando tú tú le
picked up the phone from Antonio David who
cogiste el teléfono a Antonio David que
was calling us both before me you
nos estaba llamando los dos antes que yo
tried to do the 131 mate you
me intentaste hacer la 131 colega me
tried to play the pirula on me by lying to me and we
intentaste hacer la pirula mintiéndome y
caught you in the lie me and Antonio
te pillamos la mentira yo y Antonio
David that you [ __ ] yourself when Antonio
David que te cagaste cuando Antonio
David said of of of talking the three of us in
David dijo de de de hablar los tres en
a video call you [ __ ] yourself because you
una videollamada te cagaste porque
were lying as always but
estabas mintiendo como siempre pero
come on
vamos que eso lo ha dicho el propio
Antonio David himself said that I said it and
Antonio David lo he dicho yo y lo ha
Antonio David himself said it
dicho el propio Antonio David lo ha
everyone who was
dicho todo el mundo que estuvo
involved said it  that you wanted to do the pill
involucrado que quisiste hacer la pirula
to stay Elo all for yourself man
para quedar Elo para ti solo todo tío
that's you the greedy one the one from the field
ese eres tú el avaricioso el del campo
the one with the cows what a way to
el de las vaquitas vaya manera de dar la
turn everything around hom for that already that has already been
vuelta a todo hom per eso ya eso ya se
proven but it's not that it was proven it's that
demostró pero no es que se demostrase es
he himself that by the way about that there is
que el propio que por cierto sobre eso
some news man that Salomé told me the
hay una novedad tío que me contó Salomé
other day the same Antonio
el otro día el propio el propio Antonio
Avi himself said it or so Juanjo can give it
Avi lo dijo o sea ahí ya le puede dar
the twists he wants no the
Juanjo las vueltas que quiera que no las
twists you can give it the twists you
vueltas le puedes dar las vueltas que tú
want Juanjo but things are what they
quieras Juanjo pero las cosas son las
are look precisely the other
que son mira que precisamente el otro
day Salomé told me something that a
día Salomé me comentó una cosa que un
Leo or I feel a little strange eh
Leo o me encuentro yo un poco rarete eh
man I don't know if I was continuing the salseria now or
tío No sé si seguía ahora la salsería o
go to the thread of what you were
irme aa al hilo de lo que estabas
commenting Peppa I know why you have ent
comentando Peppa sé por qué lo has ent
imagine at that moment when I talk
imagínate en ese momento cuando yo hablo
with Javi and with
con con Javi y con
Juan to stop to talk Oh a kiss a
Juan para para ha hablar Ay un beso un
kiss Laura darling Sorry I almost couldn't see you what you
beso Laura cariño Perdona casi no te veo
were commenting Peppa I know
lo de lo que estabas comentando Peppa sé
because of what you commented imagine at that
por lo has comentado imagínate en ese
moment when I  I talk to Javi and
momento cuando yo hablo con con Javi y
Juan to talk for a while about
Juan para para dar hablar un ratillo con
it and well to thank
ello y bueno para para darle gracias a
people not for for for all the support
la gente no por por por todo el apoyo
that they had shown and so on and oh
que que habían mostrado y demás y y
my goodness of course since I didn't have a
madre mía claro como yo no tenía ni
[ __ ] clue about YouTube I didn't know that the the
puñetera idea de YouTube yo no sabía que
why didn't the fight not on
el el el porqué no de de la pelea no en
my channel not on yours no because I've
mi canal no en el tuyo no porque yo he
spoken to him before because he doesn't want to
hablado antes con él porque él no quiere
do it with you because when the
hacerlo contigo porque cuando lo
really easy thing might not have been to
realmente fácil igual no hubiera sido
do it from the start
pues hacerlo de de primera hora en el
like you're doing not to broadcast a
como estás haciendo tú no emitir una
talk with me from both channels no
charla conmigo desde los dos canales no
in all honesty Jav Oliveira is what he
en honor a la verdad jav oliveira es lo
said to Juanjo at the time eh in all honesty he said let's do it
que le dijo a Juanjo en su momento eh en
both no no Antonio David doesn't
hacerlo los dos no no Antonio David no
want the truth in all honesty what I know is true I
quiere la verdad en honor a lo que yo sé
proposed to do it on both
es verdad yo le propuse hacerlo en los
channels it was my turn eh
dos canales me tocaba a mí eh tocaba mi
it was my channel and the guy didn't even want to do it on both channels at the same time but the thing is he didn't want to do it on
canal y el tío No quería ni siquiera en
both channels at the same time he didn't want to do it
los dos canales a la vez pero es que no
on both channels at the same time and he didn't want to do it
quería ni en los dos canales a la vez no
on both channels at the same time
quería ni en los dos canales a la vez ni
because I
quería que fuera el debate porque yo le
told him okay okay  Well, the interview
dije bueno Vale Venga pues la entrevista
on your channel and then on my channel the
en tu canal y luego en mi canal el
debate with the collaborators that I brought, I
debate con los colaboradores que los
brought utbh, Giovanni Carril, I brought a suit, I brought
traje yo traje a utbh a giovan carril
collaborators and that's
traje traje colaboradores y ahí fue
where he put his foot in it because if he had still kept
donde metió la pata porque si él todavía
quiet and told me
se hubiera callado y me hubiera dicho
come on, Okay, well, we'll do the debate on
venga Vale pues el debate lo hacemos en
your channel, the interview on mine,
tu canal la entrevista en el mío pero
but the greed that greed has
pero la avaricia que tiene la avaricia
made him put his foot in it because he told me,
lo hizo meter la la pata porque me dijo
No, no, it's not like the debate can't be
No no es que el debate Tampoco puede ser
on your channel either, of course, and there I went and said, and
en tu canal claro y ahí cogí yo y digo y
Antonio David told you that the debate can't
Antonio David te ha dicho que el debate
be on my channel either, and Antonio
Tampoco puede ser en mi canal y Antonio
David, who the hell is he to say what
David quién [__] es para decir lo que
can be on my channel and what can't, no, no, it
puede ser en mi canal y lo que no no no
's that he told me that it has to be like that, of
es que me ha dicho que tiene que ser así
course, and he didn't want me to talk
cómo claro y él no quería que yo hablara
to him and that's where I caught him. And
con él y ahí fue donde lo trinc Y
then I gave him when I spoke to
entonces le di cuando yo hablé con
Antony Abi on the phone, he said, Antony
Antony Abi por teléfono me dijo Antony
Abi, it's a lie, I didn't tell him that, let's
Abi es mentira yo no le he dicho eso a
see, let's make a call to the three of us. Auri.
ver vamos a hacer una llamada a los tres
Oh, now we'll see about that, Auri. Honey, I was going to
Auri Ah ahora vemos eso Auri Cariño ya
forget and he said to me, Antonio,
se me iba a olvidar e me dijo Antonio
let's make a call to the three of us.  and
vamos a hacer una llamada a los tres y
when I told Juanjo Juanjo what
cuando le dije al Juanjo Juanjo qué me
Antonio David told me that we should do a
ha dicho Antonio David que hagamos una
video call the three of us he said
videollamada a los tres se
What you want is for me to
puso Tú lo que quieres es que yo me
fight with Antonio David Oh no I
pelee con Antonio David Ay No yo no
can't make a call and the woman from behind
puedo una llamada y la mujer por detrás
hangs up real bad because he was
cuelga cuera cuera porque estaba
lying because he was lying to me she
mintiendo porque estaba mintiéndome
was trying to get it on with him
estaba intentando quedarse con topa él
from the beginning let's see in honor of
desde primera hora a ver en en honor a
the truth that I have the truth
la verdad que la verdad la tengo yo
because I was the one who lived that eh the one who was
porque yo fui quien viví eso eh el que
right in that story was Javi
llevaba razón en esa historia era Javi
Oliveira of course eh totally there's nothing
oliveira claro eh totalmente ya es que
more I mean nobody can come and
no hay más nada O sea no puede venir
tell me Hey it's not that no no no
nadie a decirme a mí Oye no es que no no
forgives or whatever because among other
perdona o sea lo que porque entre otras
things I don't earn anything there it goes okay I mean that was it was like that That was like that
cosas yo no gano nada ahí lo lleva vale
That was like
o sea eso fue fue así Eso fue así Eso
that the guy tried to do trust you the
fue así el tío intentó hacer fíate tú la
dirty trick eh I mean the guy look at the guy
guarrada eh o sea el tío fíjate el tío
the dirty trick he wanted to do I mean it wasn't
la guarrada que quiso hacer o sea no
enough for him to collaborate with me
tenía suficiente con colaborar conmigo
every week the fame that I gave him the
todas las semanas la fama que le di la
videos that I gave him and the guy when he saw
de vídeos que le di y el tipo cuando vio
the interview with Antonio David To
la entrevista a Antonio David Para
pretend what because later he wasn't
hacerse el qué porque luego no era capaz
even capable of  interview I mean no, he didn't even ask
ni de entrevistar O sea no ni una
Antonio David a question, man, he didn't
pregunta le hizo a Antonio David tío
do anything, neither the thumbnail nor
nada que no hizo nada ni la miniatura ni
the program, nothing, nothing, man,
el programa nada nada nada tío nada no
nothing, he didn't do anything, a lout, he didn't do anything, what do you
hizo nada un gañan no hizo nada que para
want, what did you want the
qué quieres para qué querías tú la
interview for, what a bunch of crap, so that
entrevista qué aranera Para que te la
I could do it there on your channel, he didn't do anything,
hiciera yo allí en tu canal no hizo nada
my goodness Juanjo, dragged everything down for
madre mía Juanjo que arrastrado todo por
money because he's going to the bar field
dinero porque se vaya al campo del bar
but no, no, but it's that you, Antoni
pero no no pero es que fite tú Antoni
Viid, acknowledged that you told the truth
viid reconoció que dijiste la verdad
about what happened with the interview
sobre lo sucedido con la entrevista
two years after the event.
pasados dos años del acontecimiento Eso
Yes, that's true, if Anton had
sí eso sí es verdad que si anton habí en
said at the time, man, what the
su momento hubiera dicho tío tú de qué
[ __ ] are you talking about? You're lying and he would have
[__] vas tú estás mintiendo y hubiera
said, pop skater and nothing. What he
dicho pop patino y nada Qué es lo que
should have done, but of course Antonia
tenía que haber hecho pero claro Antonia
at that moment didn't want problems, didn't
en ese momento no quería problemas no
want, I don't know, didn't want to get into more
quería no sé que no quería echarse más
conflict, you know, but Antonio Avi had to
conflicto sabes pero Antonio Avi lo tuvo
see it, you know, but trust me, the guy, what he
que ver sabes pero fíate tú el tío lo
wanted to do to a person with whom he was
que me quiso hacer a una persona con la
working side by side, a
que estaba codo a codo trabajando a una
person with whom he was
persona con la que estaba codo a codo
working side by side, what he won't do to a person,
trabajando qué no le hará a una persona
man, if he's following a person, he's
tío si está siguiendo a ra Está
following a person who has  threatened
siguiendo a una persona que ha amenazado
my son simply because he
a mi hijo simplemente por el hecho de
harasses me simply because he
que me acosa simplemente por el hecho de
harasses me simply because of that he is
que me acosa simplemente por eso lo está
following him he is not interested in
siguiendo a él no le interesan las
cryptocurrencies and you want it worse the
criptomonedas y lo queréis peor la la
Peppa in the thread of what this video This
Peppa al hilo de lo que este vídeo Este
video of this This interview was on the
vídeo de esto Esta entrevista fue en el
Peppa Channel and l de Troya okay
Canal de la Peppa y de l de Troya vale
This video that you are watching from Antonio
Este vídeo que estáis viendo de Antonio
David This was a call with Peppa
David Esto fue una llamada con la Peppa
and with the ar de Troya Well you know
y con el ar de Troya Bueno pues sabéis
what Peppa has deleted it Look Peppa
qué que la Peppa lo ha borrado Mira la
has deleted it no Peppa no who
Peppa lo ha borrado no la Peppa no quién
has deleted it package is already here the
la ha borrado paquete ya está aquí el
paete Look mom the package good is
paete Mira mamá el paquete buen está
here Salomé why do you say here in the
aquí Salomé por Por qué dices aquí en el
twit it is deleted if it is here looking for
twit está borrado si está aquí buscando
the click of anton vii on the
el click de anton vii en el Canal de
Peppa Channel in which he agreed with Javi it
Peppa en el que le daba la razón a Javi
turns out that he has deleted that interview
resulta que ha borrado esa entrevista
but if it is here Why do you say that he
pero si está aquí Por qué dices que la
has deleted it I don't understand Salomé you
ha borrado no lo entiendo Salomé me
told me that he was deleting it but it is
dijiste que la estaba borrar pero está
here or has he only deleted the
aquí o es que ha borrado solamente el
part Oh so he deleted the  straight
trozo Ah o sea que ha borrado el directo
to see
a ver
wait has deleted clear Peppa
espera ha borrado claro la Peppa
has only left this which is about the
solamente ha dejado esto que es lo de la
mother But she has always deleted when she talks
madre Pero ha borrado siempre que habla
to her she had sub Clear She had an
con ella tenía sub Claro Ella tenía
audience the live So Peppa has
público el directo O sea la Peppa ha
deleted the interview that
borrado la entrevista que le hizo
Antonio David did man the hatred for
Antonio David tío le puede más el odio a
Javi is more than the affection for Antonio AB Of course
Javi que el cariño a Antonio AB Claro
she Antonio AB does not give a damn
que ella Antonio AB se la suda ella lo
about the tide I tell you she is more likely to
de la marea Es te digo le puede más el
hate Javi and she has deleted that part so as
odio a Javi y ha borrado esa parte para
not to agree with me when it is
no darme la razón cuando es el propio
Antonio Aviel himself who says that I am
Antonio aviel que dice que tengo la
right eh the story
razón eh nunca va a acabase la historia
that all started with this nonsense of
que empezó todo con aqu tontería de de
the interview will never end people know
la entrevista la gente sabe
perfectly well what I said
perfectamente que fue lo que yo dije
all this eh then everything happens It is not what
todo esto eh luego pasa todo No es lo
Juan said it is true But well
que decía Juan es verdad Pero bueno no
nothing happens all the Campa what we did
pasa nada toda la Campa lo que hicimos
nobody has said that what Juanjo said was
nadie ha dicho que lo que decía Juanjo
true Juanjo nobody has
era verdad Juanjo eso no lo ha dicho
said that nobody has said that you
nadie Eso no lo ha dicho nadie te lo
are making it up nothing happens just like
está inventando no pasa nada igual que
where all this started eh that
dond empezó todo esto eh que nunca va a
the story that all started will never end
acabarse la historia que empezó todo
nonsense of the interview people
tontería de de la entrevista la gente
know perfectly well what I
sabe perfectamente que fue lo que yo
said but of course  Nobody's going to recognize him
dije pero claro nadie lo va a reconocer
because he's gone so far with Chile,
porque se llegado tan lejos con el chle
nobody's going to recognize him It's not that no no it
nadie lo va a reconocer No es que no no
's never never never never Javi deleted the
es nunca nunca nunca nunca Javi borró el
thing that said that about you how strong eh
troo que decía eso tuyo qué fuerte eh
nines how strong eh all the lies that
nines qué fuerte eh todas mentiras que
Antonio David said all Of course
dijo Antonio David todas Por supuesto
F lies and people saying Yes yes I
que F mentiras y la gente diciendo Sí sí
lied for of mat for the family But that that's not that yes he
menti por de mat por la familia Pero eso
really said it and
eso no es eso sí lo dijo de verdad and
yes no no and what makes me laugh a lot
sí no no y a mí lo que me da mucha risa
is when You hear and say No it's that it's a
es cuando Oyes y decir No es que es
response to a to a little joke wait
respuesta a una a una pullita espera
Sorry if you give in to me I don't care
Perdona si tú te das a mí me da igual
that Antonia Avil had said it No I
que Antonia avil lo hubiera dicho No yo
have it well tied up and I have everything I have I
lo tengo bien atado y lo tengo todo
even have the call gu that
tengo tengo hasta la llamada gu que
the three of us made I even have the
hicimos los tres tengo hasta la
video call the video call that
videollamada la videollamada que hicimos
the three of us made I have it look at you if look at you
los tres la tengo fíjate tú si fíjate tú
if I can prove that the
si puedo demostrar que lo de la
interview is like I say it what
entrevista es como yo lo digo qué
dirty thing did you want to do man Why
guarrada quisiste hacer tío Para qué
for two more bucks at the bank my goodness for
para dos duros más en el banco madre mía
two more bucks eh be I even have the
para dos duros más eh sea tengo hasta la
video call the video call let's see It's that I do
videollamada la videollamada a ver Es
n't want  put a screenshot of the
que no quiero poneros una captura de la
video call but I have it the
videollamada pero la tengo salimos los
three of us appear there you appear without a hat and
tres ahí sales tú sin gorra y le dice
Antonia AB says to him well nana says Antonio AB
Antonia AB bueno naná dice Antonio AB
that I saw her the other day because I was
que la vi el otro día porque estaba
organizing some things says Antonio
organizando unas cosas dice Antonio
David Well I say one thing what
David Bueno yo digo una cosa qué
argument is this you guys having can't
discusión es la que tenéis no se puede
do live shows on both channels go
hacer los directos en los dos canales ve
and says Juanjo I'm new to
y dice Juanjo Yo es que soy nuevo en
this and I don't know if that's allowed and I say
esto y no sé si eso se puede y le digo
no said yes that's what I've been telling you
no dicho si es lo que te llevo diciendo
from the beginning and you're
desde el principio y tú me estás
telling me no that Antonio David
diciendo que no que a ti Antonio David
told you that he didn't want to do it on both channels
te ha dicho que en los dos canales no
and Antonio says avid wo I've
quería y le dice Antonio avid wo Yo te
told you that I didn't want to do it on both channels and it
he dicho a ti que en los dos canales yo
stayed like that and I don't know if he
no quería y se qued así y ya no sé si
came up with something my mother my hospital my I don't
salió con algo mi madre mi hospital mi
know what you know how he gets when he's
no sé qué sabes como él se pone cuando
cornered he was brutal he was brutal because he was
se acorralado fue brutal fue brutal por
alluded to it's your problem not mine he's
aludido es tu problema no es el mío
never let go of our arm always
nunca nos ha soltado el brazo siempre
tied the satellite channels the
teido los canales satélites los
twitterers on us and everything they don't throw
twitteros encima nuestra y tod no echan
whistles they don't throw garbage she's different do you
pitas no echan basura ella es distinto
understand that it's that you have to keep
entiendes que es que hay que estar
quiet And  juo I've
callado Y juo a ti el brazo yo te lo he
let go of your arm I had you forget about himo what
soltado yo te tenía a ti olvidad himo lo
happens is that the one who hasn't stopped during
que pasa que el que no ha parado durante
all this time that we made the pact
todo este tiempo que hicimos el pacto
that you didn't fulfill, the one who hasn't stopped has
que tú no cumpliste el que no has parado
been you and I've already proven it what
ha sido tú y ya lo he demostrado lo que
happened to you is that you
a ti te pasaba es que tú en realidad
had actually made a pact because you can't stand
habías hecho un pacto porque no soportas
that I expose you but in reality you
que yo te exponga pero en realidad tú
wanted revenge against me, I mean you
querías venganza contra mí o sea te
believed that suddenly people were going to
creías que de repente la gente se iba a
turn against me that things were going to go badly for me and
poner contra mí que a mí me iba ir mal y
you've eaten what you ate maoma you've been
te has comido lo que se comió maoma has
suffering for a year and a half Oh look at
estado el año y pico sufriendo Ay mira
Joanana's sentence let's see if now they
la sentencia de joanana a ver si ahora
stop watching Javi people don't give a
dejan de ver a Javi a la gente le suda
damn about the sentence Dean is flat
la [__] la sentencia Dean plana sigue
Javi still has more audience than you Okay
Javi teniendo más audiencia que tú Bueno
then let's see if with Miare's
pues a ver a ver si con la de miare
Miare's sentence people don't give a damn about
Sentencia de miare a la gente le suda
Miare's sentence and even more so
los [__] la sentencia de miare y más
those who were in the
todavía los que estuvieron en la
story continue Javi having more
historia siguele Javi teniendo más
audience than you Okay then I'm going to bring I
audiencia que tú Bueno pues voy a traer
don't know what Maria Eugenia Yahwe nothing's
a no sé qué a María Eugenia yahwe no
wrong  don't worry we have
pasa nada no te preocupes Tenemos aquí a
trium here Marina esnal Fran cua we have
trium a Marina esnal a Fran cua tenemos
Tok here on the channel always I mean
a Tok aquí en el canal siempre o sea de
what are you up to I mean and the guy has been
qué vas tú o sea y el tío ha estado
mentioning absolutely everything I already have
mencionando a absolutamente todo ya
a live What was the name of the
tengo un directo Cómo se llamaba el
live Lili that we did and it
directo Lili que le hicimos y ahí se
shows perfectly the other day he shows
muestra perfectamente el otro día enseña
the folders the whole time in which there was
las carpetas todo el tiempo en el que se
supposed to be a pact you really gave a damn you
suponía que había pacto tú te lo pasaste
even did
por los [__] has hecho hasta directos
exclusive live broadcasts about an article that
exclusivos sobre un artículo que te que
Yoan Planas sent you to read that
te mandó yoan planas a que leyera que
his lawyers wrote you did a
escribieron sus abogados hiciste un
vertical live broadcast for that one night no
directo vertical para eso una noche no
one night no midday with a
una noche no un mediodía con una
yellow t-shirt you made an
camiseta amarilla hiciste un ridículo
incredible fool of yourself I think it was in November or
increíble creo que fue en noviembre o
around there I was with Enrique
por ahí estaba yo con el Enrique
eating and when they notified us
comiendo y cuando nos avisaron
I was like this man What is he doing What's wrong with the
me quedo así tío Qué hace Qué le pasa el
guy [ __ ] one day with a yellow t-shirt
tío cog un día con una camiseta amarilla
and he comes out a failure failure
y sale
Look There's Fran
fracasado fracasado Mira Ahí está Fran
There's Fran failure the guy with a
Ahí está Fran fracasado el tío con una
yellow t-shirt who made a [ __ ] fool
camiseta amarilla que hizo un ridículo
of himself Why did he explode like that
del copón Por qué fue que explotó así
that day that then I say Well this
ese día que luego yo digo Bueno este
this [ __ ] guy this crooked what the hell is wrong with him
este [__] tío este torcuato qué [__]
and it was because Oh Why was it
le pasa y era porque Ay Por qué era
because we had had some live with
porque habíamos tenido algún directo con
more views than him or something like that I don't
más visitas que é o alguna cosa así no
remember a move this this was this
me acuerdo una movida este este fue este
was the live look here Thank you
fue el directo mira aquí Muchas gracias
very much Solange Thank you so much for that
solange Muchísimas gracias por ese
piece of Super chat a huge kiss
pedazo de Super chat un beso enorme
[ __ ] today I didn't ask for any objective or
[__] hoy noos he pedido ni objetivo ni
anything we are here chill no aa I
nada estamos aquí chill no aá me
feel a little reolín eh I mean I don't know I
encuentro un poco reolín eh o sea no sé
feel a little bad today I think
me encuentro un poco mal hoy creo que me
the food has agreed with me eh here in this
ha sentado mal la comida eh aquí en este
live you can see how he during the whole
directo podéis ver como él durante todo
year and a half or two years he has not
el creo que año y medio o dos años no ha
fulfilled the pact never ever he has been
cumplido el pacto nunca jamás se ha ido
approaching each person that I
acercando a cada persona con la que me
was fighting with because he believed that
iba peleando porque él creía que la
people I mean if you make a pact with a
gente O sea si tú haces un pacto con una
person when you make a pact with a
persona cuando tú haces un pacto con una
person man I have made pacts with
persona tío yo he hecho pactos con
people I made peace with Danan we
personas yo hice las pases con danan que
said everything I don't know if you know
nos dijimos de todo no sé si sabéis
Who is the one that steals the contents of the
Quién es al que le roba el contenido del
beans I had them with Danan but we are
frijoles yo con danan las tuve pero
going tremendous I mean me with Danan I
vamos tremendo o sea yo con danan me
killed myself in debates in everything we talk at the
maté en debates en todo hablamos al
time when things have cooled down each
tiempo cuando ya se enfrió la cosa cada
one to his side and me  Dana hasn't
uno por su lado y a mí Dana no me ha
mentioned me again or not the only thing we
vuelto a mencionar ni mul para lo único
've mentioned each other has been for
que nos hemos mencionado ha sido para
Well but this No this what he did was
Bueno pero este No este lo que hizo fue
stop me from continuing to expose him as
frenar que yo siguiera exponiéndolo como
the liar that he is and the bad person
el mentiroso que es y la mala persona
that he is but meanwhile he's
que es pero él de mientras está
trying to stir up trouble dreaming that
intentando mover grilos soñando con que
one day the scratch is going to come to me
un día se me va a venir a mí el scratche
nobody is going to Scratch me let's see if we
a mí no me va a Scratch nadie a ver si
found out
os enterábamos
one night I was on the beach dude we
una noche estaba yo en la playa tío
were in Huelva Okay and I came to
estábamos en en huelva Vale y me vine a
Seville because Fran called me I don't know if you
Sevilla porque me llamó Fran no sé si te
remember Fran to record something with Trium
acordará Fran para grabar algo con trium
de Daniel Sancho we were going to record I don't
de de Daniel Sancho íbamos a grabar no
remember what had come out that day if it
me acuerdo que había salido ese día si
was the sentence the trial I don't remember
era la sentencia el juicio no me acuerdo
but I was on the beach and I took it and said
pero yo estaba en la playa y cogí y digo
okay let's record it because I know that it's
vale vamos a grabarlo porque sé que es
content that's going to be [ __ ] great I know
un contenido que va ir de [__] madre sé
that it's cool content and from there
que es un contenido Guay y de ahí
we'll get a video for what's left of the
sacamos vídeo para lo que queda el fin
weekend anyway I'm coming to Seville I
de semana total me vengo para Sevilla
leave my wife and the kids there in
dejo a mi mujer y los niños ahí en
Huelva at night I come here
huelva por la noche me vengo para acá
to Seville I do the live with Fran and
para Sevilla hago el directo con Fran y
with  trium 17,000 viewers we had
con trium 17,000 espectadores tuvimos
17,000 viewers that night and
esa noche 17,000 espectadores y por la y
the next day I'm at the beach and
al día siguiente estoy en la playa y me
these people send me a clip of what this
envían esta gente un clip de que está el
guy is saying at the beginning of his
gachon este diciendo al principio de su
live show well well well family well
directo bueno bueno bueno familia pues
yesterday didn't go very well the truth is that from the
ayer no fue muy bien la verdad que del
heart we were the most watched without having
corazón fuimos el más visto sin tener
anyone famous here without having
aquí a nadie famoso sin tener aquí a
any TV stars here and without
ninguna estrella de la tele y sin que
our name appearing in
nuestro nombre salga en las búsquedas de
Google searches for weird things you know because of my thing with the
Google en cosas raras sabes por lo mío
stalker because of the knife news and
del acosador por las noticias de faca y
all the nonsense these people
todas las tonterías de esta gente que
go to the press talking about me okay
van a la prensa habla de mí vale o sea
without me having done anything to him Simply
sin yo haberle hecho nada Simplemente
because we had viewers and he didn't
porque tuvimos espectadores y él no
Simply because of that eh it's true José
Simplemente por eso eh es verdad José
Luis the thing about a failure was because in a
Luis lo de fracasado fue porque en un
live show I was messing with these people
directo yo metiéndome con con esta gente
it's true with the ar de Troya the other one
es verdad con el ar de Troya el otro el
on the motorcycle said something like man you
de la moto dije algo así como tío que os
're all getting together against me and
estáis juntando todos en contra mía y a
I don't give a damn it's not that I don't give a
mí me la es que me la pela a mí no es
damn look when they start getting
que me la pele mira cuando se ponen a
together to see if they can join
juntarse entre ellos para ver si unen
forces  with against me they
todas las fuerzas con contra mí a mí me
make me big because they seem very
hacen grande porque me parecen muy
pathetic because I would tell
patéticos porque es que yo les diría a
each and every one of them to go by
todos y cada uno de ellos ir pasando
any night that I caught here
cualquier noche que me pillé aquí en
live if you want don't warn me of
directo si queréis no me aviséis de
surprises okay go by I'll let you go
sorpresa vale ir pasando yo os voy
up and you can debate with me
dejando subir y vais debatiendo conmigo
one by one or all at once if you want I
uno a uno o todos a la vez si queréis yo
have nothing to hide I have no
no tengo nada que ocultar no tengo
problem no I don't owe anything to
ningún problema no no le debo nada a
anyone no there's nothing yes yes I have done something
nadie no no hay nada si si he hecho algo
wrong at some point Or I have been wrong about
malo alguna vez O me he equivocado en
something I admit it and that's it people
algo lo reconozco y ya está la gente lo
know it you know but but of course the fact that you
sabe sabes pero pero claro que os
all have to unite against one well it
tengáis que unir todos contra uno pues
makes me big the truth makes me big
me hace grande la verdad me hace grande
and then I said something that really stuck that it was
y entonces dije una cosa que caló mucho
a fool if a fool gets together
que era de un tonto si un tonto Se junta
with another fool well they're two fools it does
con otro tonto pues son dos tontos a mí
n't hurt me and he took it that it wasn't
no me hace daño y cogió él que no iba
for him and he took it personally I mean the
para él y se dio por aludido o sea el
guy that I didn't mention him at
tío que yo no lo mencionaba para
all that I didn't
absolutamente nada que yo no lo
mention him not a [ __ ] joke I would mention him
mencionaba ni de [__] coña lo mencionaba
and the guy took it personally and took it personally and
y el tío cogió y se dio por aludido y
created a row on a Saturday at noon
formó un pollo un sábado al mediodía
okay  he made a mess just yelling at
vale formó un pollo el solo gritándole a
the camera at noon and I, he noticed
la cámara al medi día y yo yo el nota
all out of breath yelling at the camera, man,
todo sofocado gritándole a la cámara tío
what's wrong with him? And of course, then it
Qué le pasa y claro ya luego por lo
seemed that I had said that two
visto era que yo había dicho que dos
fools Well, one fool plus one fool
tontos Pues que un tonto más un tonto
is two fools and the guy had taken it
son dos tontos y el tío se había dado
personally because I said that F what And
por aludido porque yo dije eso F qué Y
that live stream was because I didn't react, I
aquel directo fue porque no lo reaccioné
didn't answer him, I saw that live stream, I
no le contesté aquel directo lo vi me
laughed and I gained 3 kilos, I mean, I think
reí y pasé 3 kilos o sea yo creo que
FJ gained 1 kilo less, who's the one who
pasó to kilo menos el FJ que es el que
comments on these things I think nobody
Comenta estas cosas Yo creo que nadie le
paid attention to that, he was left alone yelling
dio bola a eso se quedó solo gritando
at the wall and then after a while, well, yeah Yes, I
con la pared y ya luego al tiempo pues
spoke, no, it was This live stream
ya ya Sí hablé no que fuee Este directo
that I just posted but in that live stream he
que acabo de poner pero en ese directo
said some nonsense, like
que que dijo unas mamarrachadas que si
the numbers and don't say that I have
los números y no digáis que yo tengo
few views, eh Don't say that I have a
pocas visitas eh No digáis que yo tengo
lot and then the next month I decided to
muchas y ya luego al mes siguiente me
shave eh and grow a mustache
dio por afeitarme eh y dejarme El bigote
like I've been doing for the last few months
como estoy haciendo en los últimos meses
and he took it and set a goal Oh how
y cogió él y puso un objetivo Oh qué
funny that day is also not there yet
risa es ese día también ahí todavía no
Oh how funny that is  also Salomé took it
Oh qué risa es eso también Salomé cogió
and set a goal he set a
él y puso un objetivo se puso un
goal of if we reach 10 super chat
objetivo de si llegamos a 10 super chat
to 10 if we reach 10 super chat I
a 10 si llegamos a 10 super chat Me
shave everything except the mustache and now he
afeito todo menos el bigote y ahora ya
took it and said Okay yes or no should I keep
cogió y dijo Bueno qué sí o no me dejo
the mustache yes or no and he took it and
el bigote sí o no y ya cogió y se lo
let him have it what do you think trust me first
dejo que comoo fíate túa lo primero
Okay there you like it you
Bueno ya está a ti te gusta a ti te
like to be like Javi and you want to shave
gusta ser como Javi y te quieres pelar
shave like he can't but okay then it's
pelarte como él no puede pero bueno pues
okay artelo but don't make
no pasa nada artelo pero no te Montes
a show out of it as if you had two
ahí un espectáculo como si tuvieras dos
years to set a goal to
años para para hacer un objetivo para
see if you know Hey Russell how funny was that eh
ver si sabes Oy russel qué gracioso fue
How funny was the mustache thing
eso eh Qué gracioso fue lo del bigote
you guys say to me Well maybe I'll
yos que me dice Bueno a lo mejor me lo
keep it like everyone else does now
dejo como hace ahora todo el
silence no because I also know how to
mundo silencio no que yo también sé
defend myself and fight for what's mine like
defenderme y se luchar por lo mío como
you say it's my channel it's my family and it's
tú dices es mi canal es mi familia y es
my life a p it's that this job is
mi vida a p es que el trabajo este es
beautiful and he's running away
precioso y se está marchando corriendo
from seeing this nonsense and on top of that they say
de ver estas tonterías y encima dicen
like you're participating
como que tú estás participando que me
tell me when I've attacked someone
digan a mí cuánd yo he atacado a alguien
for free nobody nobody guajo nobody you messing around with sorco tilla and telling her that her daughter died because she deserves it That's not you you participated in that that was Javi's fault nobody that nobody did it I get upset when they mention topics that we
me molesto cuando mencionan en temas que
have nothing to do with but for example
no tenos nada que ver pero por ejemplo
Amador put it in the topic the
Amador lo ha metido en el temas las
cleaners for free
limpiadoras gratuitamente por la cara
just out of spite to be with
solamente por despecho estar con
us or rather but he keeps
nosotros o sea pero es que él sigue
saying that people are spiteful
diciendo que la gente tiene despecho
envious of Amador man you brought
envidia de Amador tío que has llevado
Amador to your channel and you've had the
Amador a tu canal y has tenido los
same viewers that we have
mismos espectadores que tenemos Nosotros
Right now here Eli ateli totally
ahora mismo aquí Eli ateli totalmente
free totally
gratuito totalmente
free they don't respect anything or anyone or
gratuito no respetan nada ni a nadie o
rather and then I also say one thing that I'll
sea y luego tambi digo una cosa que lo
say again She is an
vuelvo a decir Ella es una persona
anonymous person who has that I have permission
anónima que tiene que tengo yo permiso
from her to put her on my channel but
de ella para ponerla en mi canal pero
she is an anonymous person Yes yes she is an
ella es persona anónima Sí sí ella es
anonymous person and her image
persona anónima y su imagen Solamente se
Can only be put on your channel you have to ask
puede poner en tu canal hay que pedirle
leli for the right to put it on her
derecho a a leli para para ponerla en su
channel Yes yes she does not live by selling her
canal Sí sí ella no vive de vender su
life nor does she charge anything or Or rather phones that no
vida ni cobra nada ni O sea fones que no
corresponds of course and the Met in stories
corresponde claro y la Met en historias
that I told you I freak out Okay so she has
que di t flipo Vale entonces ella tiene
given me permission to be here
me ha dado el permiso de estar aquí
putting it up and talking And such But the
poniéndola y hablando Y tal Pero los
others don't have permission no it's Ah the
demás no tienen permiso no es Ah los
others don't have permission It's that he's the one
demás no tienen permiso Es que él es el
who decides or rather he's the one who decides
que decide o sea él es el que decide De
What topic can be talked about and what topics ca
qué tema se puede hablar y de qué temas
n't and that's it the rest of you can't even
no y y ya está los demás no podéis ni
criticize him or anything we have to
criticarlo a él ni nada tenemos que
go on with this with this putting up
andar con esto con esto poniendo
images like this and this [ __ ]
imágenes así y estas [__] [__]
public [ __ ] So no I don't understand I don't
público Entonces no no entiendo no
understand that for some Yes for others
entiendo que para alunos Sí para otros
no depending on what they want what
no según lo que quieran ellos lo que
happens is that it sells a lot of story in everything and that's it
pasa que vende mucho relato en todo y ya
and I think that you sound like they are
está y yo creo que sonas que son
necessary because also on the other hand
necesarias porque también otro lado
commenting on little things and I'm this was
comentar las cositas y estoy esto era
Lili pathetic no
Lili patético no
[Music]
[Música]